https://gomeyer.com/rc-cars-scooters/privacy.php

Privacy Notice
All "personal information" ("personal information" is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. Meyer Distributing reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion, and will provide notice of material changes on the home page of the Site. If as the result of such changes, you want to alter the ways in which Meyer Distributing is allowed to use your personal information, you can do so by following the procedure described below in the section titled "Updating your personal information and privacy preferences." You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, the changes to the Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Site after such notice has been posted for thirty (30) days with the following exception: If at the time you provide personal information to Meyer Distributing you are given the opportunity (as you currently are) to limit how such information will be used to communicate with you, either by Meyer Distributing or by third parties, Meyer Distributing will not change your preference in this regard without your express consent. However, if Meyer Distributing sells assets (or the assets of a division or subsidiary) to another entity, or Meyer Distributing (or a division or subsidiary) is acquired by, or merged with, another entity, Meyer Distributing may provide to such entity customer information that is related to that part of our business that was sold to or merged with the other entity without your consent.
Meyer Distributing collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. If you subscribe to a service or register a product, for example, the information is used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered users. As another example, if you enter a contest, information is collected to qualify the entry and contact you regarding the contest or prize awards. Your personal information is also used to keep you informed about product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services of Meyer Distributing and selected third parties if you have so opted to receive such communications. Meyer Distributing may collect information about the use of the Site, such as the types of services used and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. Meyer Distributing may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes. Meyer Distributing will not sell any personal information to other parties whatsoever.
Continue
Categories
Goped PartsRC Car PartsDirt Bike and Motocross PartsClearance and DiscountsJet Ski PartsTools and Oil
What's New?
Maddog Brake Pads$10.49
Information
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Conditions of Use
Contact Us
Shopping Cart
0 items
Bestsellers
Goped Tire and WheelGo-Mix Goped Oil PacketEngine Mount Screw for Goped and RC CarGoped Air Filter Kit UFOGoped Gas TankGoped Inner TubeGoped Short Drive SpindleMeyer Racing Long DriveGoped Gas Tank CoverGoped Gas and Fuel Line Blue 1/8"
Manufacturers
Please SelectADA Racing Part..Goped ScootersK&N Air FiltersMeyer RacingSunline Perform..TGN - Team GoNa..
Reviews
Totally worth the money to replace stripped out Phillips scr...
Specials
Goped Pipe Manifold$9.50$8.99
